本電影為第三方制作的同人電影
其中包含了赤裸的性暴力和杜撰的場面.
代號：瓦倫丁
開始的電影        特殊功能                 設置
F.O.W.模式                                   簡單模式
生化危機
Resident Evil
本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
那是在9月份的一個普通的日子
that all begin is in ordianary day in  september.
Ordinary day in Raccoon City
在浣熊市中普通的一天
浣熊市阿克雷山脈 北
一直平穩的家庭生活消失了,現在這里卻充滿了危險
Stable family life has gone, now here is full of danger
浣熊城警察局
過去這個城市在保護傘公司的控制下淪為了地獄
the city once controll by Umbrella Corporationhas willing intrully gone the hell
死尸們率先沖破街道,吞噬啃咬著鮮肉從我眼前掠過.
the leading dead that around with four secend streets turn flash from (bonein front of my eyes.
整晚我都沒有見過單獨的幸存者,事情變得更糟了
i've not see the single survour all night,and it make matters worse.
有什么東西在獵殺我,讓我感到有些不對勁
somthing is hunting me,someting sanister
我希望威斯克在這,真的希望如此.時間緊迫,但我卻不知道該做什么
I wish cause Wesker were here. I really do,time shortened  I have no idea what cause the operate .
但是我一定要走下去,或者死亡
but i'am get to botton this or dead trying.
吉爾·瓦倫丁 結束
juil violen time  out
該死
shit
我走錯了,這里到處都是
am i deep   every where
救命
help
死神附身：（Die~Die~Die~hehehehehe）不對……是Death （死亡）
混蛋！離我遠點！
bastard.get away from me
你是什么東西
what are you
不
no
你要做什么？
what are you
不！你不能這樣
no,you can't!
救命
help
我不會……讓你有下次的！
I so where……you next time
我要殺了你,我一定會這樣做…
I'll kill you,i'am get a make sure you are……
這太..大了
it's terri.....big
求求你
please
死亡
Death
求求你了
please
救命！！！走開！！救命！
help ! get away!  help!
你為什么要幫我
why did you help me?
死亡
Death
讓我走吧！我快死了
let me go! i will die now
不！你不能這樣！
you can not! you can't!
請你離開
Please you leave
你可以幫我的
you can help me like this
死亡！哦！耶！！！！！！
Death o  ye！！！！
（磁磁磁電波聲）在那里,4號跟蹤到了,所以可以再次去執行任務了.
&#@￥！
找到她的位置了，她沒有外傷
got it locate here.no hard deal concise.
天啊,什么也沒有
jesus !nothing one to more learn.
收到
well roger
@#@！#￥
收到
roger that.
跟在我后面
here with me ass.
你找到她了么
have you found her?
是的，但是我認為*#@！#
yes. but I think *#@！#
吉爾  嘿  吉爾 吉爾·瓦倫丁
juil....hey ..juil!juil violen time
非常感謝你這一次終于回應了我
Thank you very much for the last time you noticed me
好吧 我希望不是其他人.小聲點 ,杰克
well,i hope it's not about someone elsebe quite jerk.
除此以外，你總能和我保持聯系
besides,you always keep up with me.
好吧,聽起來你準備好了
well,sounds like you Ready  for more.
這很不錯
It's so good
你知道這總讓我有所準備
you know that always gets me ready.
我現在就想要
I want it now
我們應該嘗試生更多的寶寶在這
We should try to give birth to more babies in this
克里斯？ 克里斯？
Cries？Cries？
我他媽在哪
where the hell i‘am in
看這個驕傲的小公舉
look’s like a pretty princess she‘s vainly even
炒雞棒的驚喜
brilliant offer surprise
釋放piw實驗體  3..2..1..
eleasing first PIW test 3..2..1
讓我們拭目以待
let’s see will it begins
負邊界（育種嘗試）非自然抵抗是有顯著的.
negative bounding on the （breeding attempt ）  unnatural resistance is remarkable.
真令人失望（不是我們希望的）
disappointing that‘s  （not them for see）
第二學科是正確的,長官.好的,好的,我看到了.
subject two is agree sir.  yes,yes,i’ll see then.
噢！不！
oh！ no！
不！ 讓我走！
no！...no..let..me go...
噢！ 不！不！
OH! NO..NO....
育種感染已采取
negative bounding infect to has taken
當惡魔強暴瓦羅丁的時候,你的結果真讓我失望
my demon‘s  violent time must you keep disappointing me！
長官,我應該停止實驗么
shall i abolish the tests sir?
育種繼續,釋放 HANA（血細胞凝集素神經氨酸酶）.長官,還沒準備好,它還不穩定.
negative full ! introduce to a hantan. sir that bow is not ready. But sir his unstable.
不知道會發生什么,博士還會這樣做嗎？  立刻釋放生物體！馬上！
Don't know what will happen, Dr. will not do this? release the creature! now!
你準備好抓住今晚的個機會.聽從內部人員
you ready clinging this said tonight .with it's inside.
是的 長官
yes sir
檢查武器安全
weapon's check out security.
開始報告
start to this report
生命體征穩定,她在蘇醒
Vital signs stable stable .she‘s  holding
操！為什么停下來！
why is fucking that on hold.
好吧..足夠了.
well...enough
先生,你在干什么？  這樣偏高的數值
對保護者會產生影響的！ 你管的太多了,孩子.
What are you doing？sir,that’s the menu overhigh with for profect.....  over time by your concern！boy.
這里我說的算！不要忤逆我！除非你想被送走
but i'am the header inside here .dont rebellious with my head,if you don't deliver.
上帝！我們都做了什么！
good god! what have we done.
先生？？ 噢！上帝！
sir? oh god!
所有人！！馬上出去！
everyone out! now!
為什么
WHY?
恭喜,我的情人
Congratulations! Miss. Valentine.
是個男孩
It's a boy.
翻譯:T君
看到我身后的紅銹色天空下的那片區域了嗎？
Can you see that area behind me, beneath the red tainted sky?
那就是陸戰隊導彈襲擊浣熊市后留下的痕跡
That is what’s left of Raccoon city after the military fired a missile ass
據未經證實的報道,該導彈為核彈.如果情況屬實
那么在城市中的十萬居民中很幾乎不可能有幸存者
According to unconfirmed reports, the missile was legitly nuclear. If this is indeed the case, then there is little hope of finding any survivors among the cities of one hundred thousand inhabitants.
翻譯:閑晴
翻譯：人民
我們需要知道是誰授權這次軍事打擊
What we need to know is who authorizes this missile strike.
翻譯：雨
某人：我認為這是絕對的恥辱類型,絕對的恥辱.所以你應該了解它.
Someone: I think it’s  an absolute disgrace genre, an absolute disgrace. All you should load of it.
時軸：T君
白宮外的抗議持續到第9天
The protest outside the White House continued into day 9
時軸：人民
壓制：雪夜
總統先生,保護傘公司與這次生物災害事件之間有什么聯系？.
Mr. President, what is the connection between Umbrella corporation and this Bio-hazard incident this time.
總統已宣布辭職…
The president has announced with resignation…
今晚美國總統將出席華盛頓宣布辭職.
Announces the break-into is coming out to Washington tonight, the president of United States has sensationally resign trip of his.
今晚浣熊市中間的巨坑就是這次的事故造成的...
Hollow up in Raccoon city, that’s on top story tonight and join in these...
保護傘公司的首席執行官奧斯威爾·斯賓塞今天在正在燃燒的浣熊市罪惡作證.
Umbrella’s CEO Oswell Spencer is expected to encore today to testify in the ongoing Raccoon drops.
正在進行的法律案件對保護傘公司進行造成負面影響…
The ongoing legal case against the Umbrella drags on …
我們活過今晚的人提名揭發保護傘公司所有罪惡的事實…
We will live to the  tonight where Umbrella Corporation was found guilty on all charger…
曾經的85年,法律與撲熱息痛的戰爭…
Antique-85 year, the legal battle against paracetamol giant…
奧斯威爾·斯賓塞,您對此有什么看法嗎？
(Oswell Spencer, any thoughts on the rolling?)
顯然,我們對法院的判決非常失望.目前我們還沒有進一步評論.
Obviously, we are very disappointed with the court’s decision. I have no further comments at this time.
好吧,那么世界范圍的藥物陰謀論呢……我的意思是,拜托,你們真的相信這些東西嗎？
ok again, what about this worldwide pharmaceutical conspiracy … I mean, come on, are you guy really believe in that stuffs?
三聯公司否認其毫無根據的說法…
The Tricell corporation refused its baseless claim …
保護傘公司的股票在歐洲暴跌.嚴重打擊了商業巨頭們,很多商業巨頭因此解散
The Umbrella corporation stock plummeted here in Europe. This delta has serious blow to the business giant resulting in its complete dissolution.
為什么要花很長時間才能推翻保護傘公司的證據？
Why is it taking so long for evidence against Umbrella to appear?
嗯,關于這一點,有很多流行的理論.
Hmm… well, there are  a lot of popular theories about that one.
通過檢查核心記錄可以看出,最可能的原因已經
公布于眾,這一證據可能會牽連多個政府,包括我們...
Take a look at the core records, the most likely reason now this evidence has gone public is that it continues this information will incriminate many ruled governments, including our own…
預計的受害者的人數從數十萬上升到…
The estimated number of bio-terror victims has skyrocketed from hundreds of thousands to ...